TALHA JAVED

WEB DEVELOPER

Johar Town, Lahore 0322-6905140 talhachughtai 1122@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

I am a web enthusiast and researcher, a quick learner, and keen to explore the realm of web engineering. To work and grow professionally as a web developer in a stable organization where I could contribute my skills. My endeavor and dedication in the job will help me achieve the company's goals and objectives.

TECHNICAL SKILL

PHP Laravel SQL Jquery
ReactJS Mongoose NodeJS ExpressJS

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Computer Science

2017 - 2022

The University Of Lahore, Lahore
Object Oriented Programming, Datab

Database Systems, Data

Structures, Machine Learning

Intermediate in Computer Science

2015 - 2017

Govt Post Graduate Degree College, Sheikhupura Mathematics, Physics, Computer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Laravel Devoloper Intern 365 Care Private Limited, Lahore

July,2022 - Oct, 2022

Junior Laravel Developer 365 Care Private Limited, Lahore

Oct, 2022 - Present

- Designing and building web applications using Laravel.
- Working with front-end and back-end developers on projects.
- Maintaining web-based applications.
- Troubleshooting issues in the implementation and debugging of builds.
- Ensure HTML, CSS, and shared JavaScript is valid and consistent across applications
- Continuously discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency.

TALHAJAVED

WEB DEVELOPER

Johar Town, Lahore 0322-6905140 talhachughtai 1122@gmail.com

CERTIFICATIONS

Machine Learning Foundations: A Case Study Approach

University Of Washington

Credentials:https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ABCWcwd4XiR9

R3yFWmpztOvbloLXQ22j/view?usp=sharing

Aug,2021

Neural Networks and Deep Learning

Deep Learning.Al

Credentials:https://drive.google.com/file/d/19Decvh3gx6SOD1Q

1GvOlVlrBfuODWqM9/view?usp=sharing

Sep,2021

Introduction to Cloud Computing

IBM July,2022

<u>Credentials:</u>https://drive.google.com/file/d/1w35XKEFbl-2LQVOY2OzU11gBeaLoNOdd/view?usp=sharing

PROJECTS

- HRMS ON LIVE (PHP, LARAVEL, JQuery, AJAX)
- Property Management (PHP, LARAVEL, JQuery, AJAX)

HOBBIES

- Traveling
- Hiking
- Video Games
- Movies